fbbonline.in 2019-04-07

# Privacy Policy

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent and we only use your information as described in the Privacy Policy. We view protection of your privacy as a very important community principle. We understand clearly that you and Your Information is one of our most important assets. We store and process Your Information on computers located in the India that are protected by physical as well as technological security devices.

 **Sharing of Personal Information:**

We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates. These entities and affiliates may market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-out.

We may disclose personal information to third parties. This disclosure may be required for us to provide you access to our Services, to comply with our legal obligations, to enforce our User Agreement, to facilitate our marketing and advertising activities, or to prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate fraudulent or illegal activities related to our Services. 

By signing up with fbbonline, you consent to the use of your email / mobile number, to reach out to you,with promotional content.

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process.

We and our affiliates will share / sell some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity, or re-organization, amalgamation, restructuring of business. Should such a transaction occur that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.

 **Use of Personal Information:**

We use personal information to provide the services you request. We use your personal information to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; collect money; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our Website.

We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

We may occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. We use this data to tailor your experience at our Website.

 **Third party links**

fbbonline may contain links to third party websites (websites controlled by companies other than fbbonline). The third party websites are regulated by their respective privacy policy and are not under the control of fbbonline. Customer willing to access the third party website shall do it at their own discretion and are requested to go through their respective privacy policy. fbbonline shall not be held responsible for any contents or default arising out of linked website.

 **Accessing, correcting and deleting of information**

fbbonline provides the customer with the option of accessing their personal information stored in the website. Customers may at any time access the information provided by them and update the information in case of inaccuracy. Customer shall also have the option of deleting the stored information, in case they feel their information is not safe with the website.

 **Posting of information in public areas**

The information posted by the users in the public areas such as chat box, comment box, or in the online forums of fbbonline are free to the access of other person and www.fbbonline.in has no control over it. fbbonline shall not be held responsible for the use of such information by any third party.

 **Cookies**

fbbonline use cookies for improving and customizing customer shopping experience. Cookies are a piece of a data which is sent by the website and stored in the user web browser. It helps the website to load user’s previous activity anytime when the website is reloaded. fbbonline use cookies to keep a track on user’s activity so that it can recall your given information and preferences, every time when you load the website thereby making your use of the website faster and convenient. Use of cookies may also store your password for accessing the website so that you can automatically be directed your account on the website. Cookies do not carry viruses nor install malware on the host computer. However, the use of cookies is optional and it is upon the discretion of the user to accept or decline cookies. User may also change their browser setting to decline all or any of the cookie. Accepting the cookie is not essential for accessing www.fbbonline.in, but declining cookie may prevent you from accessing some features of the website thereby restricting your use of the site.

**Web beacon**

Web beacon, also known as pixel tag or web bug is a transparent graphic image used in combination with cookies to observe the behavior of the user of the website. The web page contains a web beacon which would enable us to count the users visiting the page in order to deliver co-branded services. These web beacons collects a limited information like the page on which it resides, cookie number, time and date of page view and do not collect any personal information. Web beacons would be declined automatically by declining the use of cookies. The web beacon on fbbonline is not permitted for the use by third party.

**User consent**

By continuing to use fbbonline and providing us with your information, you consent to our privacy policy and permit us to use your information in the manner set in fbbonline privacy policy.

 **Changes to privacy policy**

fbbonline reserves all the right to make changes in the privacy policy without prior notice to the user. Such changes will be posted on this page and will come to effect on the date of posting of such changes in the privacy policy page. fbbonline assure that such changes would not lessen the protection promised to the users for securing their privacy.

 **Contact**

If you have any queries regarding the privacy policy or feedback or suggestion, feel free to contact us at care@fbbonline.in.
